Please insert coins!
Okay, the magic energy flow is normal.
Boxo, forgive me if this
is none of my business,
but if you wish to speak with Lammis,
I'd happily relay your thoughts.
That's right.
I could have much deeper
conversations with
Lammis if I were to rely on Kikuyu's help.
Thanks, M-O. Understood.
Please forgive me if such
a request is presumptuous.
It's okay. Thanks!
I'm touched, but the first time I really
talk to Lamas, it'll be on my own.
There we go, and success!
Right, let's proceed through in order.
We can start with Kikuyu's group.
Perfect.
Thanks so much, Hulani.
And lastly, it's our turn. Yeah. I'll
activate it. Go ahead. Hello there!
What's going on?
Whoa, what's with this red light?
This makes no sense.
I found nothing out of
the ordinary with it.
Oh, I don't want to be
away from Botto again.
I don't want us to be
apart anymore either.
If we could at least
all stay in one group.
I know.
Activate barrier.
Please just let it send
us all to the same place.
On the outside I'm just a big metal box
but inside I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of
wonders I travel to and
fro on the back of my
super strong partner.
Llamas the name's Boxo hello
there that means yes by the way.
Boxxo, Hulemy!
I'm glad you're both here. Me too.
Thank goodness we're
all together. But where?
I've never seen this room before.
This is maddening.
There was nothing wrong
with the transfer circle.
And everybody else went
through with no problem.
What gives?
Uh, Hulemy?
I might be wrong, but I saw something
strange when we transferred.
It looked like some kind of red
light coming from on top of Boxo.
Huh?
Lamas, I owe you one.
The malfunction spell.
It was cast on Boxo,
not the transfer circle.
Wait, what do you mean?
There's a damn magic symbol
right here on Boxo's top corner.
I'll get rid of it.
That's a start, at least.
My top corner? Oh, crap!
That's when it happened!
He really got us good.
What a pain in the butt to have
as an enemy, that trickster.
All right, there should be
no malfunctions next time.
Seems like we'll have
to wait a few days for
the Transfer Circle's
magic power to recharge.
Huh, this is the seventh stratum.
Um, so is that the Dark Forest Stratum?
Yeah, I hear it's a pretty dangerous
place inhabited by lots of plant monsters.
Although from the look of
things, nothing's been destroyed.
What?
Why is a tree growing right
in front of the entrance?
And the way it's shaped, it looks like...
It looks like a person. How creepy.
Creepy is right.
I've heard that there are monsters on
this stratum that turn people into trees.
It's bad news for women,
children, and the elderly.
People who can't put up a fight.
Hearing that, it's even
harder to look at them.
Someone must be here. Over there.
I'll happily deal with the carrot beanies.
These monsters' bodily
fluids can be toxic.
If any gets on your boots, I
shall clean them off later.
I've been wanting to fight some monsters!
Your help is appreciated.
Ubuntu!
I've been waiting for you!
Please don't shake too hard! Shwing!
Calm down!
I almost forgot how good his meat is.
You ain't kidding.
It's nice to have meat again.
I'm so sick of veggies.
This place is naturally verdant all around
a field bursting with vegetables aplenty.
Meat, however, is surprisingly scarce.
Aha!
No wonder they're wolfing it down.
Mishuel isn't with you? He's not.
Only Shui and I were sent
to this stratum, apparently.
Interesting.
Well, with Mishuel's strength, he's
probably fine, no matter where he went.
It's weird.
With all these people turned into trees,
you'd think at least some
houses would be destroyed.
The monsters of this stratum are extremely
reluctant to harm any vegetation,
even felled trees.
I imagine they consider the
wood planks kindred beings.
That's crazy!
Then I guess that means
they get really angry
when you cut down trees to build a house,
doesn't it?
It does indeed.
Apparently you must go to great
pains here to cut down even one.
Those strange trees we saw in the
village, were they once people?
Yes.
Those are the women, children,
and people of a certain
age who inhaled the Stratum
Lord's pollen during a
previous monster attack.
It's horrifying to see.
I'm shocked anyone survived.
Stratum Lords are formidable.
Did they defeat it?
Oh, heavens no.
They merely drove it away with fire,
but they only use it as a threat for
fear it could burn down the village.
Oh, I see.
I recall fire being banned on this
stratum, so that does make sense.
Indeed it does.
They could easily defeat
the Stratum Lord with fire.
But the trees of this stratum are
especially vulnerable to heat and flame.
The people who turned into trees,
is there a way to turn them back?
I believe so, if the
stratum lord is defeated.
Oh, that's good.
But it seems like it
would be really hard to
find a stratum lord in a
giant forest like this.
Actually, finding the stratum
lord is the easiest part.
That's it there.
Huh? What?
That giant tree guy?
That thing looks taller than a skyscraper!
How does that thing ambulate without
crushing all the trees in the forest?
I believe that's one of the
Stratum Lord's powers, in fact.
When it does move, all the
trees scamper out of the way.
A Stratum Lord that can control
plants in a forest, huh?
That doesn't sound like
it'd be easy to deal with.
We can delve further into
that subject tomorrow.
Look at our comrades.
They're in no condition.
I can't eat anymore.
I'd say Shui won't be
of any use for a while.
I guess that means guard
duty is up to us right now.
You know,
it feels like it's been forever since you
and I got to be alone together like this.
Now that you mention it,
it does feel like forever.
This might be kind of weird
to say, so don't get mad.
But I have this feeling that I can
do anything as long as I'm with you.
Aw, thanks, Lamas.
I feel that way too.
Yes, thanks!
Thanks seems like an odd thing to say.
Huh?
What's with this deep, tender vibe?
Whoa.
Uh, Lamas?
Wait a minute.
Um, what's happening? Is she...
Don't tell me this is the
start of a kitschy rom-com
between an inanimate object
and his girl best friend!
Oh right, I forgot we
were on watch. Too bad.
Yeah, we gotta take it seriously.
Whoa!
You're telling me you've been
eating these monsters lately?
That's right.
The vegetable monsters here actually
taste pretty good in their own way.
A little gamey, though.
Besides,
there's plenty of lumber around here,
so luckily I won't run out
of arrows any time soon.
Shui!
As requested, I brought
you more arrows. Thanks!
You got it.
Oh, that's Boxo on your back, so
you must be the blessing of my girl.
The name is Lamas.
Oh, okay, then. Sorry about that.
Rumor has it that you
fight bare-handed, Lamas.
Is that true?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, that seems like a waste
for your blessing of might.
Come on over to my shop.
I'll find you a damn good weapon.
Oh!
So this is an otherworldly weapons shop.
But, like, I don't even need any weapons.
It can't hurt to look.
And he said you could have whatever
you want as thanks for Boxo's food.
Ha-ha!
I knew there'd be all kinds of cool stuff.
Huh, I'm surprised to see some
with magic stones built into them.
So, my friends, what do
you think of my shop?
Feel free to browse at your leisure.
What's this? Oh, that one?
It's water repellent.
Good in the hot or cold,
and it performs wonderfully.
But it's also flashy.
And it's not for sale.
What do you think, Boxo?
Thank you very much.
Hold on a sec.
Did you just give me a compliment?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm really surprised by
how good it looks on her.
But then, just about anything
would look good on Lamas.
Oh, I think we should try to
get him to sell it to us later.
Now then, this one's a type of magic item.
They get heavier the
moment you pick one up.
Measuring stones, huh?
That's a pretty unusual
magic item you've got there.
You sure know your stuff.
Well, go on.
Try it out, why don't you?
Oh, it's so light.
Nah, you just make it look easy.
Want to try holding it, Hulemy?
Sure, why not?
Hand it over.
Oh!
Lama's taking it!
Take it now! Ah! Close call.
There was almost a hole in the floor.
Okay, let's skip over one.
Try and pick up number three.
Whoa, are you serious?
Yeah, this one is super light, too.
Well, how about the one at the end, then?
It's about as heavy as Boxo. Really?
This is incredible!
You're even stronger than I thought!
Right!
I'm gonna make you your ultimate weapon!
I hope you're ready! Dang!
This weapons merchant guy
is practically on fire!
You really do that? Heck yeah! I'm on it!
You know, we have yet to meet
the director of this stratum.
We dropped by the
Hunters Association right
away when we went to all the other strata.
Do I know Director Dark?
No, I haven't met him as a matter of fact.
Lamas, do you know what he's like?
Well, let me see.
I would characterize
him as cheerful and fun.
He's a good fit for
the Stratum's director.
Yeah, he's not a bad guy by any means.
What are these two not telling us?
If you're curious about the director,
this might be the perfect timing.
Hey, nice to meet ya!
You can call me Director Dark if you like!
Honestly, I'd be thrilled if
you just remembered my face!
I mean, how many guys do you have
me who look like a creepy shadow?!
That's the part where
you're supposed to laugh.
Darkness Fiend's my race, you see.
That sounds all impressive, but my
vibe's all about having fun, bro!
I'm a real party guy at heart!
I might be a Darkness Fiend,
but I like to keep things light!
My days are all hectic and messy
thinking about it makes me tired.
I gotta sit down But it's my opinion
that as director I've got to do
my best to be dignified no matter
how much it goes against my nature.
Oh, yeah You guys are from
Clearflow Lake Stratum, right?
How's that cuddly director bear doing?
I bet he keeps busy,
too Doesn't he say every day is
just a turtle bear to get through?
He talks like a man's eye performer
and this hail of cheesy jokes
is denting my surface I would
characterize him as cheerful and fun.
He's a good fit for
the Stratum's director.
He's not a bad guy by any means.
That explains why those two
didn't come along to introduce us.
Hey, Boxo, why so stiff?
You nervous? Hey, loosen up!
Oh, I guess you're always the stiff.
From what I'm told, Boxo
dispenses unusual food and drink.
Now that's what I call a magical item.
What's that you say?
I should try it for myself.
Don't mind if I do it, much obliged.
I don't want to encourage him,
but this guy's a director.
I guess I have to be nice to him.
You really can make stuff
float through the air!
Just spectacular!
Never had a floating machine drink before.
That's tasty stuff.
Like, really tasty.
More than I'd expect from sweet tea.
Now if only I had a
sweet tea pie by my side!
Get it!
Big mistake.
I'll have to listen to dad jokes forever
if I don't do something, and quickly.
There's gotta be some way to outdo him.
I've got it!
Form change!
A manzai vending machine.
What's happening?
Hello, people.
How are you?
Hey, full house tonight.
Thank you for coming
out to see us, friend.
Look at that front row.
We got a pretty girl, pretty girl.
Oh, skip that one.
Pretty girl? Cut that out.
I ever tell you about how my mom
can't remember her favorite novel?
Huh, maybe I can help.
What is it about?
The main character goes to another world.
Oh, sure, when a guy goes to
another world, that's an easy guy.
Watch and learn from
the old school, buddy.
Nothing easy about it, friend.
He's a difficult guy
having a real hard time.
What a coincidence.
I'm also having a hard
time with a typical guy.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for coming out today, folks.
Hopefully this puts him
in his place for a while.
Huh?
We'll fell some trees to create a path.
If the monsters seem too
dangerous, we'll come right back.
Our goal this time is to measure
how powerful the enemies are.
Here comes our grand welcome.
Shall we deal with them first?
Like you even have to ask.
He seems like a total joker,
but apparently Director Dark used to
be in the same group as Director Bear?
so they fought side by side.
I bet he's pretty handy
in a fight, goofy or not.
I don't recall putting
veggies on my chopping list.
For the sake of my sanity, I'm
going to pretend I didn't hear that.
Lamas, there are fewer enemies now.
Please remove some of the trees.
Okay!
Oh, that's an amazing sight!
I'm just getting started!
Let's get started!
Lamas, let's call it a
day and head back. Okay!
That's how we spent the next few days,
clearing trees and extending
the path through the forest.
We've covered a lot of ground,
but there's been no movement.
I'm beginning to think it might be
faster to just go look for the commander.
Oh, there you are.
I've been looking for you.
Botan, Kuroyata, and Director
Baron Kikuyu! Hey, friends!
Whoa, how'd you get here?
I thought the transfer circle wouldn't
be usable for two or three days.
You want to know how we got here?
Well, the flow of magic power
seems to have settled a bit?
So I tried directing
it from the other side.
and I was able to activate
the transfer circle that way.
Wow, not a bad idea.
But it would take someone
with your skill to do it.
Skill is one upside of growing old.
It's been a long time, ma 'am.
Well, well, it's the
girl with the appetite.
Shui is your name, yes?
I'm sure that mess with
the captain was difficult.
Don't worry, I put all that behind me now.
My butt's asleep, are we there yet?
Yeah, and is it time to eat?
Shirley said lack of sleep
is the arch enemy of beauty.
What's that mean?
They even have the band
of gluttons with them.
Now Team Traveling Zoo is complete.
All the soft, cozy animal
time one could ever want.
All right, it's time to face the
music and go see Black Black.
Huh?
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
My back pain just started flurrying
up out of nowhere in the match page.
Are you okay, Gramps?
I'm so sorry, but I need to tend to him.
I'm afraid I won't be able to...
Don't even try it, you two.
Come on, you both know I
can't deal with him alone.
Ah, he means Director Dark.
Let's head back.
Fine.
Kikoyu, take care of you-know-what.
Yes, I'd be honored to. Huh?
What was that all about?
Boxxo, Director Bear asked me for a favor.
Would you mind helping?
A favor?
The people currently in this village.
Is that everyone on this stratum?
That's right.
It's about time for me to distribute food,
so I think they're all going to gather.
Then as we discussed before, I will
hand out your products to each of them.
Hello there!
Here you are.
Um, your name is Kikoyu, isn't it?
Well, thank you.
Thanks a lot, little lady.
Here you are.
I've figured out what Kikoyu has in mind.
Right!
I'll record her face.
Kikoyu was reading minds
as she handed over the
box lunches in order to
search for the commander.
This person.
She is the Netherlord's commander.
That's one of my hunters!
That youngster's been working
hard here on this stratum,
and I had high hopes for her!
I had no idea she was working
for the Netherlord! I see,
but we don't know whether she was hiding
it all along or was persuaded to defect.
Now then, what do we do next?
We should get information out
of her immediately, but how?
Oh, I know!
We have just the man for the job.
That is an option.
Heavy, we would like you to
arrest and question the commander.
Do you have any thoughts about that?
Ah, yes, I see.
I'd be happy to.
I can use hallucinations to gather
information, or perhaps affect her emotionally.
Well,
when it comes to apprehending the villain,
you'd better leave the arrest up to me.
This scandal happened on my watch,
so it's up to me to set things right.
I couldn't read his expression, but
I could sense he was really angry.
As director, I imagine he
wants to clean up this mess.
Actually, anyone know where she is?
Okay, here she comes.
This room's well soundproofed.
Nobody's going to hear this.
Hey, boss, take it from here.
I will use my sensory manipulation
to deactivate her sense
of touch and pain and make
her believe she is dreaming.
I will alter her vision to make
her think she sees the netherlord,
but she will still be able to hear, so
please refrain from speaking while I work.
If her sense of touch is muted, she
won't know if somebody touches her.
I am speaking to you in your dream.
Can you tell who I am?
The Netherlord.
Whoa!
He must really appear to
her as the Netherlord!
Then recount for me the circumstances
under which you first began working for me.
Yes, sir.
About two months ago, you
appeared before me as a human.
You said if I obeyed you,
you'd give me enough money
to pay off my gambling debt
and live the rest of my
life without having to work.
What did I tell you to do?
While purporting to defend
the people as a hunter,
I would use this ring to
order the monsters to attack.
Correct, and is that all you can remember?
About two weeks ago, I met with
members of the Menagerie of Fools,
new recruits of yours.
They seemed to be looking for someone,
but they left as soon as they
realized they weren't here.
So the captain and crew
dropped by this stratum.
They were probably looking for the
two remaining Menagerie members.
One last thing.
Could you take off those
boots and show them to me?
Bro, don't forget you're
the Netherlord right now!
Um, you want my boots?
For some strange reason, I'm
finding it difficult to move.
Then I shall carefully remove them myself,
so that the scent gradually wafts
out and makes its way to my nose!
Director.
This is rich.
You've always had a problem with gambling.
But I always thought you could change!
When I'd loaned you money before,
you said you'd never gamble again!
I'm a dope for believing you!
Well then, that takes
care of the Commander.
All we've got left now is to turn
those trees back into people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not my journey.
It's broken.
It's still not there.
I've got a letter to the letter.
I've got a letter to the air.
you could even win a reward i
look forward to serving you again